[rock guitar riff playing]
‎好激动
This is so exciting.
‎我们的第一台电脑
‎我感觉像柯克船长
Oh! Our first computer.
‎我们的第一台电脑
‎我感觉像柯克船长
I feel like Captain Kirk.
Oh.
‎还有 奥兹 你真贴心 还帮我们安装
And, Ozzie, you are a doll
for helping us set it up.
‎我就不明白 我们要这东西干嘛
I don't understand why we need that thing.
‎雷德 这是未来所趋
It is the future, Red.
‎咱俩至少有一个人得跟上时代
One of us has to stay hip
and current with the times.
‎快看 还带着个小踏板
‎就像我的缝纫机
Oh, look.
‎快看 还带着个小踏板
‎就像我的缝纫机
It comes with a little foot pedal
like my sewing machine.
‎不 那是鼠标
No, that's the mouse.
Oh.
‎鼠标是干什么用的？
What does a mouse do?
‎在你阁楼里拉粑粑
It craps in your attic.
‎放轻松点 雷德
Lighten up, Red.
‎美国正步入线上 咱们也得出份力
America is going online.
Let's do our part.
‎如今我们可以
‎了解时事、体育、政治资讯了
Now we can read about
current events, sports, politics.
‎我已经在了解了
I do that already.
‎这个叫报纸
It's called a newspaper.
‎知道我喜欢它什么吗？
And you know what I love about this?
‎它不与政府连线
No wires connected to the government.
‎这东西跟政府连着吗？
Is this thing connected to the government?
‎是的 总统现在就能看到你
Yes, the president can see you right now.
‎我知道你在开玩笑
I know you're kidding.
‎不过 万一你是认真的
But just in case you're not…
‎嗨 比尔 我超爱看你上深夜秀
Hi, Bill. Loved you on Arsenio.
[funky rock music playing]
‎内特 你要二手热水浴缸做什么？
Nate, why would you want a used hot tub?
‎里面糊得净是别人的体液
It's gonna be contaminated
with other people's juices.
‎是啊 我们也可以糊
[chuckles] Yeah.
Until we contaminate it with our juices.
‎好浪漫
That's so romantic.
‎妮可 这个不要钱
‎除了它 也就还有只山羊是白给的
It's free, Nik.
The only other free thing is a goat.
‎我爱你 但我不想跟你共享山羊
I love you, but I am not sharing a goat.
‎万一咱俩分手呢？山羊归谁？
What happens if we break up?
Who gets the goat?
‎我父母离了婚 信我一句
‎最好还是别逼山羊做出选择
As someone whose parents split up,
you don't wanna force the goat to choose.
‎明天你自己去取那恶心的二手浴缸
Nate, go get your disgusting
used hot tub tomorrow.
‎我们约了去“魅力摄影”拍照
We have an appointment
to get our pictures done at Glamour Shots.
‎没关系
Oh, it's cool.
‎可以等我的小胡子长出来
‎再去“魅力摄影”
We can rebook Glamour Shots
for when my mustache comes in.
‎那就是“遥遥无期”咯
Oh! So in, like, 1990-never.
‎闭嘴 格温 我喝牛奶时
‎差不多就能看出来呢
Shut up, Gwen!
When I drink milk, you can almost see it.
‎听着 妮可 这东西可是先到先得
Look, Nik. This hot tub is
first come, first served.
‎机会不等人
‎之前我就是这么错失超大狗笼的
It can't wait.
That's how I lost that giant dog crate.
‎-你没养狗
‎-但我可能会得到一只山羊
-You don't have a dog!
-But I might get a goat.
‎我受够了
-I'm done.
-[scoffs]
‎你都不跟我好好沟通感情
You never want
to talk about our relationship.
‎感情 是吧？
Relationships, right? [chuckles]
‎感情有啥用？
Who needs 'em?
‎那你不介意我们只做朋友咯？
So you're okay with us just being friends?
‎必须的 这多好 我喜欢
Pfft. Oh yeah, it's great. I love it.
‎好得很
It's so good.
‎又爽又开心
It's so good and fun.
[breathing rapidly]
‎你的策略奏效了
‎他的憨男脑都烧短路了
Your move worked.
You short-circuited his boy brain.
‎就像玩电子游戏卡住了
It's like he's glitching in a video game.
‎妮可 我可不会
‎继续守在这里看你不理人
Okay, Nik, I'm not sitting here anymore,
listening to you not talk to me.
‎杰伊 跟我去取热水浴缸不？
Jay, wanna help me pick up this hot tub?
‎好啊 干啥？
Sure. What?
‎-兄弟！
‎-嗯 我来了
-Bro!
-Yeah, I'm coming.
[rock music playing]
‎长者电脑日干活累了？
Taking a break
from old-people computer day?
‎我试着跟你奶奶解释
‎什么是“虚拟桌面”
I tried to explain the virtual desktop
to your grandma.
‎然后还得解释“虚拟”
Then I had to explain the word "virtual."
‎后来不知怎的 还得解释桌子
Then somehow I had to explain a desk.
‎你不是非得帮她
You really don't have to do this for her.
‎这不是为了她 而是为了我
It's not for her. It's for me.
‎她只是大计划的一部分
‎我想向你奶奶出柜
She's part of a bigger plan.
I want to come out to your grandmother.
‎哇 好吧
Wow. Okay.
‎我…你看起来那么自信
‎我以为大家都知道了
I… You seem so confident and self-assured.
I thought everyone knew.
‎我是个生活在威斯康辛小镇的小同志
I'm a gay kid
living in small-town Wisconsin.
‎法院停车场还有拴马的地方
There are still parking spots
for horses at the courthouse.
‎对我来说 向任何人出柜都是大事
The fact that I'm out to anyone is huge.
‎我可以体会 七年级时 我挣扎了很久
I can relate. In seventh grade,
it took me a really long time
‎才跟父母说我想从单簧管改吹双簧管
to tell my parents
I wanted to switch from clarinet to oboe.
‎但最终还是成了
But I got there.
‎你也可以的
And you will too.
‎是啊
Sure.
‎绝对是一码事
That's the same.
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do but talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎你为什么想向我奶奶出柜？
So why do you want to come out
to my grandmother?
‎这是我16步出柜计划的第七步
She's step seven
in my 16-step coming out plan.
‎原来出柜还得分步
I didn't know there were steps.
‎每年在棕榈泉开会
‎我们都会更新步骤
They're updated every year
at our conference in Palm Springs.
‎我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
[chuckles]
‎我知道
‎我有同性恋朋友 也有所了解
I knew that. I know things.
I have a gay friend.
‎你在说我吗？
Is it me?
‎对的
Yes.
‎如我之前所说 我在朝最终阶段迈进
As I was saying,
I'm working my way towards the final step,
‎向父母坦白
telling my parents.
‎我刚完成了第六步
I've just completed step six,
‎向仅有一面之缘的陌生人出柜
coming out to strangers
who I'll never see again.
‎不好意思 我想你打错了
I'm sorry.
I think you have the wrong number.
‎还有…我是同性恋
Also… I'm gay.
‎不用找了 我是同性恋
Keep the change. I'm gay.
‎我是同性恋！
I'm gaaaaay!
[yelling fades]
‎弹起来的时候 我又跟他说了一遍
I told him again when I bounced back up.
‎接下来是第七步
‎向时常见面的成年人出柜
Next is step seven, coming out
to an adult who I see all the time.
‎也就是你的奶奶
AKA, your grandmother.
[chuckles]
‎太好了 她特别喜欢你
That's perfect. She loves you.
‎所有女人都喜欢我
All women love me.
‎真可惜
What a waste.
‎你能不能帮我探探路？
But can you feel her out for me?
‎我只想确定是否找对人了
I just want to make sure
she's the right person for me to tell.
‎找她没问题的 我奶奶比谁都贴心
She'll be great.
No one's sweeter than my grandma.
‎我的奶奶瞅着也很贴心
‎除非你在公共场合哺乳
My nana seems sweet
until you try to breastfeed in public.
‎那她就会往你脸上呲香水
‎还会骂你是破鞋
Then she'll spray perfume in your face
and call you a whore.
[rock music playing]
‎在这儿呢
[excited gasp] There it is!
[exclaiming]
‎这比我们上次发现那片裸体海滩还爽
This is even better than that time
we found that nude beach.
‎然后就看到我的棒球教练压弓步
Until we saw
my baseball coach doing lunges.
‎我现在的人生就这种感觉
That's what my life feels like right now.
‎一个松垮垮、软塌塌的蛋蛋
A sandy, saggy sack.
‎兄弟…
Bro…
‎你因为莉亚丧成这样 我看着好郁闷
It is really bumming me out
seeing you this down about Leia.
‎知道干啥能好受点吗？
You know what
always makes you feel better?
‎女阴手 来吧
Vagina hands. Get in here.
[both laughing]
‎-好精准
‎-这才是好玩的地方
-It's so accurate.
-That's what it makes it fun!
‎妹妹不见了 痛苦又回来了
Well, now that it's gone, the pain's back.
[door opens]
‎你们好 小伙子
Hello, boys.
‎你好 女士 我们为浴缸的事来过电话
Hello, ma'am. We called about the hot tub.
‎哦 对
Oh yes.
‎能转手真是太好了
I'll be glad to see it go.
‎这东西以前是我先生的
It used to be my husband's,
‎他去世后 我就没再怎么用了
but since he passed away,
I don't use it very much.
‎我很遗憾 他是怎么死的？
Oh. I'm so sorry. How did he die?
‎他是淹死的
He drowned.
‎-你还想要热水浴缸吗？
‎-杰伊
-Still want the hot tub?
-[whispers] Jay.
‎他是在湖里淹死的
Oh, he drowned in a lake.
‎太好了！
Yes!
‎我是说 请节哀顺变
I mean, I am so sorry for your loss.
‎我只是…不想要个闹鬼的热水浴缸
I just… really did not want
a haunted hot tub.
‎那我们要了
We'll take it.
‎稍等 你们不想先试试吗？
Now, hold on.
Don't you want to try it out first?
‎你们觉得够热吗？
Is it hot enough for you, boys?
‎是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
‎刚才是谁的脚？
Whose foot is that?
‎我喜欢这个游戏
Oh, I love this game.
[funky rock music playing]
[strains]
[loud computer chime]
‎凯蒂 快过来
Kitty, come in here.
‎你需要什么？
What do you need?
‎它醒了
It woke up.
‎嗯 挺可爱的
Well, that is so cute.
‎我一小时前让它睡了 现在肯定饿了
I put it to sleep about an hour ago.
It must be hungry.
Oh. [chuckles]
‎现在它死了
Now it's dead.
‎没事
That's okay.
‎他对艾瑞克一开始也没好脸色
Took him a while to warm up to Eric too.
‎嗨 奶奶 我能问你点事吗？
Hey, Grandma, can I run something by you?
‎这事有点敏感私密
It's kind of sensitive and personal.
‎是青涩话题吗？我好怀念这样
Is it teenager stuff?
[gasps] I've missed this.
‎对 是关于我朋友的
Yeah, it's about my friend.
‎明白 你朋友 好的
Got it. Your friend. Right.
‎我跟艾瑞克也经常聊他那些“朋友”
I've had a lot of these "friend" talks
with Eric.
‎他的“朋友”尿床了
His "friend" wet the bed.
‎他的“朋友”迷上了一个老师
His "friend" had a crush on a teacher.
‎他的“朋友”下身被橡皮筋勒住了
His "friend" got a rubber band
stuck on his privates.
‎总之…
Anyway, um…
‎你听完这件事 可能会觉得不舒服
It's about something that might be
outside of your comfort zone.
‎是毒品吗？你应该告诉你朋友
Is it drugs?
Because you should tell your friend,
‎刚开始只是罐啤酒 没等你反应过来
it starts with a beer,
and before you know it,
‎你就吸粉睡公园了
you're sleeping in the park
hooked on the crank.
‎不关毒品的事
It's not drugs.
‎我不能明说 但这事很重要
I can't really say,
but it's… it's a big deal.
‎这样做需要勇气
‎因为迈出这一步 就回不了头了
And it's scary because,
once you do it, there's no going back.
‎好的 明白
Got it. Okay.
‎那就告诉你朋友
‎什么时候找我聊都可以
Well, you tell your friend
that I am ready to talk whenever they are.
‎谢谢奶奶 你是最酷的
Thanks, Grandma. You're the coolest.
‎没错 泰然自若就是我
That's me. Cool as a cucumber.
‎唐娜 我是凯蒂 你女儿要尝禁果了
Donna, it's Kitty!
Your daughter is about to have sex!
[rock music playing]
‎真奇怪 你我从来没单独一起玩过
This is weird.
You and I never hang out by ourselves.
‎为什么？
Why is that?
‎我对你没意见
It's nothing bad.
‎我只是喜欢跟别人玩
I just prefer other people.
‎我也是
Me too.
‎你哥哥居然为一个热水浴缸把我扔下
[scoffs] But your brother
ditched me for that hot tub.
‎他愿意洗澡 你就知足吧
Just be happy he's gonna take a bath.
‎我好无聊
[groans] I'm so bored.
‎我们要不要找点事做？
Should we do something?
‎一起吗？
Together?
‎-我也没无聊到那种地步
‎-嗯 我也是
-I'm not that desperate.
-Yeah, no, me neither.
‎我们毫无共同点
We have nothing in common.
‎好吧 我们有一个共同点
Okay, we have
one thing in common. [chuckles]
‎必须的
Totally!
‎等等 我的手链呢？
Wait, where's my bracelet?
‎我不知道 我没见过
I don't know. I haven't seen it.
[snickers, laughs]
‎你真有趣
You're fun!
‎你也很有趣
‎要不组个趣葱圈？
Should we be Funyuns?
‎趣葱圈！
Funyuns!
[rock music playing]
‎只要点一下这里 就可以上网了
Just click right there,
and you'll be online.
‎现在感觉好紧张
I have butterflies in my stomach
‎感觉就像新开了一卷保鲜膜
just like when I crack open
a new roll of Saran Wrap.
‎第一下撕错了地方
‎接下来六个月都不好过
If you start that off wrong,
the next six months are ruined.
‎按一下就对了
Please, just click it.
[dial-up modem screeching]
‎好吧 互联网就是两个小魔兽对吼
Oh, okay, the internet is just
two demons yelling at each other.
‎-形容得还挺形象
‎-就是
-That's actually pretty accurate.
-Yeah.
‎在继续之前 我有件事想跟你说
So, before we continue, there is something
I wanted to talk to you about.
‎呃…
It's, uh…
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎你好像很紧张
‎是不是把马桶给塞了？
You seem nervous?
Did you clog up the toilet?
‎这不怪你 我家管道太老旧
It's not your fault. We have old pipes.
‎是我自己的事 我和别人不太…
[sighs] It's actually about me,
and how I'm different from--
‎她人在哪？
Where is she?
‎莉亚 妈妈来了 赶紧给我下来
Leia, it's Mom! Get down here!
‎莉亚！
Leia!
‎一路还顺利吗？
How was your drive?
‎路上堵得厉害 我溜边溜了11公里
There was a big traffic jam, so I did
about seven miles on the shoulder.
‎妈妈 你怎么来了？
Mom, what are you doing here?
‎就是这小子？
Is this the boy?
‎这就是你的小禁果？
Is this your sex boy?
‎什么？
What?
‎我跟你妈妈说了你朋友犯冲动的事
I told your mom
about your friend and her urges.
‎我给你买了避孕套、凝胶、海绵
‎还有我能找到的最难看的内裤
I got you condoms, jellies, sponges,
‎我给你买了避孕套、凝胶、海绵
‎还有我能找到的最难看的内裤
and the ugliest underwear I could find.
‎-安定？
‎-那是给我的
-Valium?
-Those are for me.
‎妈 我没想发生性行为
-Mom, I'm not having sex.
-[sighs]
‎好吧 那你想告诉奶奶什么秘密？
Okay, so then what is this secret
you were telling Grandma about?
‎其实吧 我是想发生性行为
Actually, this is about me
wanting to have sex.
‎找个男生…在床上
With a guy. [chuckles]
In bed.
‎还有…其他干这事儿的地方
And, um… other places
where people do that to each other.
‎你来得正好 她荷尔蒙指数都爆表了
You got here just in time.
Her hormones are exploding.
‎没事做时 就画鸡鸡
Constantly drawing penises.
‎都魔怔了
She's obsessed!
Shh!
‎总统会听到的
[whispers] The president can hear you.
‎好吧 听着
Okay, look.
‎你没有草率行事
‎而是坦诚告诉我们 我为你骄傲
I am proud of you for opening up to us
before you did anything.
‎-也许我们该谈谈性事了
‎-我们谈过了
-Maybe it's time we have the sex talk.
-We had that talk.
‎那时候讲的都是
‎什么妹妹、棍棍、洞洞的
That one was all nay-nays,
nah-nahs, and hoo-hoos.
‎这次要用专有名词了
This time, we're using the real words.
[hip-hop beat playing]
‎嗨 圈儿！
Hey, Funyun.
‎-咋啦 圈儿？
‎-你现在想做什么？
-Yeah, Funyun?
-What do you want to do now?
‎有件事我和内特经常一起做
Well, there's something
I normally do with Nate,
‎但跟你一起应该更好玩
but I think it'd be
so much more fun with you.
‎（魅力摄影）
["Here Comes the Hot Stepper" playing]
-♪ Here comes the hot stepper ♪
-♪ Murderer ♪
-[shutter clicking]
-♪ I'm the lyrical gangster ♪
-♪ Pick up the crew in de area ♪
-♪ Murderer ♪
-♪ Still love you like that ♪
-♪ Murderer… ♪
[shutter clicking]
[song fades out]
‎（避孕套）
‎-好了 莉亚 现在你对我说
‎-那些词我说不出口
Okay, say it back to me, Leia.
‎-好了 莉亚 现在你对我说
‎-那些词我说不出口
[sighs] I can't with the real words.
‎好吧 那怎么舒服就怎么说
Okay, whatever you're comfortable with.
‎一旦棍棍进了妹妹 就不能进洞洞
Once a nay-nay's been in a nah-nah,
it can't go in a hoo-hoo.
‎等等 棍棍是哪个来着？要不这样？
Wait, which one was the nay-nay again?
You know what?
‎不管啥进过啥 都别往啥里放
Don't put anything
into anything after it's been in anything.
‎妈妈 我们真的不用搞这么大阵仗
Mom, we really didn't need to go this far.
‎我的确有喜欢的男生 我对他有想法
There's a boy I like, and, yeah,
I've had some thoughts about him.
‎他有件吊腰的T恤衫…
Like, he's got this one T-shirt
that rides up a little…
‎我超嫉妒 真希望我是那件T恤衫
I'm jealous, Mom.
I want to be the T-shirt.
‎要来真的了
Oh, it's happening!
‎没有啦 我都还没吻过他
It's not happening.
I haven't even kissed him yet.
‎你告诉他你的感受了吗？
Okay, well, have you told him
how you feel?
‎算是吧
Sort of.
‎但搞得一团糟 我完全不得要领
[sighs] It's kind of a big mess.
I'm so bad at this.
‎这是家族遗传
It runs in the family.
‎-你也是？
‎-我？不 是你爸爸
-You too?
-Me? No. Your dad.
‎不管尝试多少次…他总是会搞砸
But no matter how many times
he messed it all up,
‎但我总会回到他身边…
‎因为他有一颗赤诚之心
I always found my way back to him…
because he has a good heart.
‎就像你一样
Just like you.
‎等等 也就是说
‎老爸没有他说的那么厉害
Wait, so Dad wasn't as smooth
as he says he was.
‎这么说吧 你能出生算走运了
Let's just say, you're lucky you exist.
[rock music playing]
‎玛丽安 我觉得很迷茫
I just feel so lost, Marion.
‎我都认不清我自己了
I don't know who I am anymore.
‎失去拉尔夫时 我也有过这种感觉
I went through the same thing
when I lost Ralph.
‎我的整个世界都被颠覆了
My whole world turned upside down.
‎我就是那种 玛尔
I'm so there, Mar.
‎但你能够适应 然后向前看
But you can adapt. You move on.
‎人生还有更多惊喜等着你
Life has more surprises waiting for you.
‎太深刻了
That's deep.
‎我之前也是这么说的
‎只是没有亡夫而已
That's basically what I said
but without the dead husband stuff.
‎奶奶 不可以 我说过了
‎别再把男人骗进你的热水浴缸了
Grandma! No!
‎奶奶 不可以 我说过了
‎别再把男人骗进你的热水浴缸了
I told you to stop tricking guys
into your hot tub.
‎什…没有啊 我们只是拿走前先试试
Wha… She didn't do that. We're just
trying it out before we take it.
‎兄弟 这就是骗人的地方
Bro, I think that's the trick.
‎我楼上有张免费的大床
‎如果愿意的话 可以试试
I've got a free king-size bed upstairs
if you'd like to try that out.
‎-免费的？
‎-兄弟
-It's free?
-Bro!
‎-对不起 她浪费了你们的时间
‎-不 不算浪费
-Sorry she wasted your time.
-No, it wasn't a waste.
‎我最近正失落 她给了我很好的建议
I was getting down on myself,
and she gave me really good advice.
‎是啊 她总爱帮帅哥
Yeah, she always helps out the cute ones.
‎我要找《省钱一族》举报你
I am reporting you to the Pennysaver.
Ooh!
[funky rock music playing]
‎抱歉 我淡定的家人
‎搅合了你的关键时刻
Sorry your big moment
was hijacked by my very chill family.
‎没关系
It's fine.
‎在回家的路上
‎我告诉了过境警卫 以保持功力
On the way home, I told a crossing guard,
just to stay sharp.
‎好了 准备好听点肉麻的
Okay. Brace yourself for some sap.
‎谢谢你昨天帮我打掩护
Thank you for covering for me yesterday.
‎你不必这么做 但这对我意义非凡
You didn't have to do it,
but it really meant a lot.
‎当然了 奥兹
Of course, Ozzie.
‎虽然你说我画鸡鸡 给我挖坑
You kind of threw me under the bus
with the penis stuff,
‎但我就当你是慌不择路吧
but I'll chalk that up to nerves.
‎我当时很慌 心里这么想就这么说了
I panicked, and that's
what I was thinking about, so I said it.
[soft knocking]
‎好了 莉莉 我走了
All right, Le-Le, I'm out of here.
‎只能走正道的话 路上的用时得翻倍
It's gonna take me twice as long
if I can only use the real lanes.
‎-好的 妈妈 爱你
‎-爱你
-Okay, Mom. Love you.
-Love you.
‎-很高兴认识你 奥兹
‎-我也一样
-Nice to meet you, Ozzie.
-You too.
‎看来莉亚的美貌是随了妈妈
I can see where Leia gets her good looks.
‎你真讨人喜欢
Oh! You're a little charmer.
‎你俩确定不会发生关系？
You sure you aren't gonna have sex?
‎-确定
‎-绝对的
-Positive.
-A million percent.
‎按下回车键 就能登录邮箱了
Just hit enter
and you'll be signed in to your email.
[rhythmic mouth noises]
‎你有邮件
‎我的天 我收到了邮件 太刺激了
-[male voice] You've got mail.
-Oh my God, I've got mail.
‎我的天 我收到了邮件 太刺激了
Oh! This is thrilling.
‎虽说我生过娃 但这个也相当刺激
I mean, I've had kids,
but this is right up there.
‎其实 邮件是我发的
Actually, that's from me.
‎我有话一直想跟你说 打开吧
There's something I've been trying
to tell you, so go ahead and open it.
Oh?
‎好
Okay.
‎双击一下小邮箱
Double-click on the little mailbox.
‎天啊
Oh dear.
‎跑哪儿去了？
Where did it go?
‎就在这里
It's right there.
Oh.
‎点啊点
-Click-click!
-[mouse clicks]
‎不 是角落里的小邮箱
No. The little box in the corner.
‎-全没了
‎-在这后面
-The whole thing is gone.
-It's behind there.
‎-在啥后面？
‎-那个窗口
-Behind where?
-That window.
[loud computer chime]
[Ozzie huffs]
‎重启 那…
Restarting. So…
‎我们得等五分钟
We have about five minutes.
[sighs]
‎算了
Forget it.
‎福尔曼太太
Mrs. Forman.
‎我是同性恋
I'm gay.
‎我知道很久了 现在想告诉你
I've known for a while now,
and I wanted you to know.
‎我还有个叫艾蒂安的男友
‎他住在加拿大
I even have a boyfriend,
Etienne, who lives in Canada.
‎我不知道对此该作何感想
Well, I don't know how I feel about this.
Oh.
‎我朋友莎朗就嫁了一个加国人
‎他把莎朗的丰田旅行车偷跑了
My friend Sharon married a Canadian man,
‎我朋友莎朗就嫁了一个加国人
‎他把莎朗的丰田旅行车偷跑了
and he made off with her Toyota wagon.
‎车里还放着她猫咪的骨灰
‎可把她坑惨了
And her cat's ashes were in there,
and she is a mess.
‎但…你不介意我是同性恋吗？
But… you're okay with me being gay?
‎当然不介意
Well, of course I am.
‎好孩子 到这儿来
Oh, sweet boy, get in here.
‎你让我觉得自己很特别
You just made me feel really special.
[chuckles softly]
[inhales, exhales sharply]
‎这就是你帮我装电脑的原因吗？
Is that why you helped me
with the computer?
‎不 是因为我喜欢
No, I did it because I loved it.
[laughs giddily]
[rock music playing]
‎那个…昨天 是吧？
So… yesterday, huh?
‎真没想到
Very unexpected.
‎我们…？
Did we…?
‎玩爽了没？必须的 两回呢
Have fun? Yeah.
We did.
‎玩爽了没？必须的 两回呢
Twice.
‎-还是别提这件事了
‎-秘密带进坟墓里
-Let's never talk about this again.
-Secret dies with me.
‎妮可 坐这儿吧
Sit here, Nik.
‎我要拿这片生菜去喂山羊
I'm gonna take this lettuce
out to my goat.
‎你不会吧
You did not.
‎不要钱的呀
It was free, Nik!
‎你现在是山羊妈妈了
You're a goat's mommy now.
‎好吧 真可爱
Okay, that's cute.
‎好了 第七步搞定 接下来呢？
So, step seven is in the books.
What's next?
‎-我偷了辆车
‎-真的吗？
-I steal a car.
-Really?
‎没有 我告诉了我的儿科医生
No, I tell my pediatrician.
‎天啊 杰伊进来了
Oh God. Jay just walked in.
‎还穿着那件小T恤
He's wearing that tiny T-shirt.
‎我的天啊 他累的时候越发帅了
Oh my God. He's even hotter
when he's tired.
‎你说这友情牌 我还要打多久？
How long do I keep
this friend thing going?
‎难说 是你出了这不着调的主意
I don't know. It was your crazy-ass idea.
‎去找他谈谈就是了
Just go talk to him.
‎我该怎么说？
What am I supposed to do?
‎在番茄酱跟前
‎对他说出我的爱？太可怕了
Profess my love to him in front of
the ketchup pump? That's so scary.
‎我刚跟你奶奶出柜
‎你连跟知道你心意的男生说出心意
I just came out to your grandma.
You can tell a guy who knows you like him
‎都不敢哇
that you like him.
‎-那是妮基的发箍吗？
‎-什么？
-Is that Nikki's scrunchie?
-What?!
‎不是
No. [nervous chuckle]
‎嘿
Hey.
‎嗨
‎还记得那天晚上
‎我说只想跟你做朋友吗？
Um, so you know how the other night
I said I just wanted to be friends?
‎是啊 真意外 还是不好受那种
Yeah. That was a surprise,
and not the fun kind.
‎那我接下来要说的 你肯定爱听
Well, then you're gonna like
what I'm about to say.
‎抱歉 停车费了好大功夫
Sorry. It took me forever to park.
‎你的朋友在停车场追着一只山羊乱跑
Your friend is chasing a goat
around the parking lot
‎还有一个女生冲他吼叫
while some girl yells at him.
‎咱们第一次约会至少有件趣事
At least we'll have a story
for our first date.
‎赛琳娜 这是我朋友莉亚
Oh, Serena, this is my friend Leia.
‎你好 朋友
Howdy, friend!
‎我就是…来打点番茄酱
I was, uh, just getting some ketchup
from the big ol' pump.
‎雷德？
Red?
‎你在做什么？
What are you doing?
Uh…
‎没什么 回去睡觉吧
Nothing. Go back to bed.
‎雷德福尔曼 你把手拿开
Red Forman, move your hands.
[Red groans]
‎这是拉蔻儿薇芝？
Is that Raquel Welch?
‎还真是！
[gasps] It is!
‎雷德福尔曼
Red Forman.
‎你用新电脑了 我真高兴
I am so happy
you're using the new computer!
‎好了 帮我找找柯克道格拉斯的
Now, find me one of Kirk Douglas.
[Red clears throat]
‎-穿角斗士装那种
‎-好
-In his gladiator outfit.
-Oh… Okay…
‎尽情享受吧
Have at it.
[clicking mouse]
[loud computer chime]
‎重启中
Restarting.
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu